Register of the Socialist Workers Party Records, 1928-2002
Wisconsin Historical Society
- Part 1 (Micro 596, Micro 816, Micro 993, Micro 1078, Micro 2015, Micro 2050, AC 588, CB 131): Original Collection, 1928-1993, Micro 596; 185 reels of microfilm (35mm) and 2 films
  - Activities and Organizing Records
    - Anti-war work, 1965-1975
      - Warren, James Mac (Immigration) case, 1987-1988 (Reel 37, Frame 287)
      - Wounded Knee, 1974 (Reel 37, Frame 424)
      - Zahraie, Committee to Defend
        - General, 1972-1974 (Reel 37, Frame 453)
        - Clippings (Reel 37, Frame 683)
        - Legal documents (Reel 37, Frame 716)
        - Meeting notes (Reel 37, Frame 784)
    - Gay rights, 1970-1987 (Reel 38, Frame 1)
    - International Solidarity
      - SWP Internal Records
        - African Liberation Day, 1972 (Reel 39, Frame 3)
        - Angola, 1974-1976, undated (Reel 39, Frame 12)
        - European refugees
          - American Committee for European Worker Relief, 1946-1950 (Reel 39, Frame 102)
          - American Fund for Political Prisoners and Refugees, 1938-1939, undated (Reel 39, Frame 205)
        - France (Committee to Defend the French Students), 1968-1969 (Reel 39, Frame 231)
        - Greece, 1947 (Reel 39, Frame 447)
        - Iran
          - Committee for Artistic and Intellectual Freedom in Iran, 1973-1979, undated (Reel 39, Frame 470)
          - Defense of SWP political prisoners, 1979 (Reel 39, Frame 736)
        - Ireland, 1969-1976, 1985, undated (Reel 39, Frame 776)
        - Korea, 1974 (Reel 39, Frame 847)
        - Mexico, 1967-1970, undated (Reel 39, Frame 857)
        - Palestine/Israel
          - Committee on New Alternatives, 1969-1971 (Reel 39, Frame 897)
          - Israeli frame-ups, undated (Reel 40, Frame 3)
          - Palestinian solidarity, 1973-1974, 1982 (Reel 40, Frame 12)
        - Puerto Rico, 1973-1974, undated (Reel 40, Frame 92)
        - South Africa
          - Alexander Defense Committee, 1965-1968 (Reel 40, Frame 146)
          - ADC vs. Justice Department, 1966, undated (Reel 40, Frame 380)
          - Alexander on nationalism, undated (Reel 40, Frame 432)
          - Brutus, Dennis, 1965-1966 (Reel 40, Frame 446)
          - Koka (Drake) tour, 1972, 1978 (Reel 40, Frame 462)
          - Lee, Franz, tour, 1964-1966 (Reel 40, Frame 475)
          - New York University Conference, undated (Reel 40, Frame 533)
          - Sihali, Eunice, 1966-1967 (Reel 40, Frame 538)
          - Soweto student tour, 1976-1977 (Reel 40, Frame 560)
          - Tabata tour, 1965-1966, 1970 (Reel 40, Frame 565)
      - Fair Play for Cuba Committee, 1960-1980
        - Constitutions and by-laws, undated (Reel 41, Frame 3)
        - Chapter correspondence
          - California (Reel 41, Frame 22)
          - Canada (Reel 41, Frame 127)
          - Colorado (Reel 41, Frame 160)
          - Connecticut (Reel 41, Frame 175)
          - Florida (Reel 41, Frame 180)
          - Illinois (Reel 41, Frame 188)
          - Indiana (Reel 41, Frame 218)
          - Iowa (Reel 41, Frame 232)
          - Massachusetts (Reel 41, Frame 238)
          - Michigan (Reel 41, Frame 256)
          - Minnesota (Reel 41, Frame 357)
          - New York (Reel 41, Frame 367)
          - Ohio (Reel 41, Frame 535)
        - Clippings, 1960-1961 (Reel 41, Frame 577)
        - Literature and reprints (Reel 41, Frame 601)
        - Publicity, undated (Reel 41, Frame 682)
      - U.S. Committee for Justice to Latin American Prisoners, 1967-1977 (Reel 41, Frame 747)
    - Oppressed Minorities
      - General documents on Black struggle
        - 1942-1977 (Reel 42, Frame 4)
        - 1978-1979, 1985-1987 (Reel 43, Frame 4)
      - Subject files
        - Black nationalism and the SWP, Classes by Robert Vernon, undated (Reel 43, Frame 198)
        - Black Panther Party, 1965-1973, undated (Reel 43, Frame 314)
        - Boston anti-racist activities, 1974-1975 (Reel 43, Frame 727)
        - Crusade for Justice, 1974, 1976-1977 (Reel 43, Frame 800)
        - Freedom Now Party, 1963-1964, undated (Reel 44, Frame 2)
        - KKK, 1979 (Reel 44, Frame 75)
        - Latino/Chicano/Puerto Rican liberation, 1970-1987 (Reel 44, Frame 93)
        - Malcolm X, letters on Militant Labor Forum, 1989 (Reel 44, Frame 287)
        - Miscellaneous black freedom projects, 1974-1976, undated (Reel 44, Frame 293)
        - National Black Independent Political Party (NBIPP)
          - General records, 1980-1986 (Reel 44, Frame 369)
          - Reference file
            - Background material (Reel 44A, Frame 3)
            - Convention and meeting files, 1980-1985 (Reel 44A, Frame 28)
          - Subject files
            - Clippings, 1980-1983, undated (Reel 44B, Frame 182)
            - Daniels speech, 1981 (Reel 44B, Frame 249)
            - Grenada, 1983 (Reel 44B, Frame 268)
            - Informational Bulletin, 1983 (Reel 44B, Frame 295)
            - Miscellaneous committees, 1981-1982 (Reel 44B, Frame 300)
            - NBIPP Partyline, 1981-1984 (Reel 44B, Frame 353)
            - SWP controversy, 1981-1984 (Reel 44B, Frame 377)
            - Warren, Mac, Review of NBIPP accomplishments, 1983, 1985 (Reel 44B, Frame 454)
            - Washington, Harold, 1984 (Reel 44B, Frame 587)
          - NBIPP Local files
            - Atlanta, 1982-1983 (Reel 44B, Frame 598)
            - Baltimore, 1981-1985 (Reel 44B, Frame 607)
            - Birmingham, 1981-1982, undated (Reel 44B, Frame 653)
            - Detroit, 1981, 1985, undated (Reel 44B, Frame 689)
            - Indianapolis, 1981, 1981 (Reel 44B, Frame 697)
            - Jersey City, undated (Reel 44B, Frame 702)
            - Los Angeles, 1981, 1984 (Reel 44B, Frame 714)
            - Milwaukee, 1982 (Reel 44B, Frame 763)
            - Minneapolis, 1983, undated (Reel 44B, Frame 768)
            - Miscellaneous locals (Reel 44B, Frame 777)
            - New York state, 1981, 1986 (Reel 44B, Frame 789)
            - North Carolina, 1981-1982 (Reel 44B, Frame 860)
            - Oakland, 1981-1983 (Reel 44B, Frame 865)
            - Ohio, 1981-1983 (Reel 44B, Frame 880)
            - Philadelphia, undated (Reel 44B, Frame 930)
            - Pittsburgh, 1981 (Reel 44B, Frame 937)
            - Virginia, 1981 (Reel 44B, Frame 946)
            - Washington, D.C., 1981-1986 (Reel 44B, Frame 966)
          - SWP documents, 1980-1986
        - National Black United Front, 1981-1985 (Reel 44B, Frame 672)
        - Native Americans, General, 1976 (Reel 44B, Frame 739)
        - Weber affirmative action case, 1979 (Reel 44B, Frame 751)
    - Trade Union files
      - General
        - 1937-1945, 1967-1974 (Reel 45, Frame 1)
        - Caribbean unionists, 1987 (Reel 45, Frame 437)
        - Engels, unidentified notes (Reel 45, Frame 447)
        - Rasmussen, Paul, Tribute to packinghouse workers, circa 1940 (Reel 45, Frame 470)
      - Fraction files
        - Automobile fraction
          - 1947-1951 (Reel 45, Frame 514)
          - 1955, 1963, 1970-1971 (Reel 46, Frame 3)
        - Electrical fraction, 1950-1951, 1983 (Reel 46, Frame 48)
        - Machinists, 1980 (Reel 46, Frame 233)
        - Maritime fraction, 1936-1950, 1983, 1987 (Reel 46, Frame 264)
        - Mineworkers fraction, 1979-1989 (Reel 46, Frame 627)
        - Paperworkers, 1988 (Reel 46, Frame 689)
        - Railroads
          - 1944-1946, 1970-1978, 1988-1989 (Reel 46, Frame 728)
          - Right to Vote Committee, UTU, 1970-1971 (Reel 47, Frame 3)
        - Retail clerks, 1949 (Reel 46, Frame 927)
        - Rubber fraction, 1946-1949 (Reel 47, Frame 134)
        - Steel fraction, 1941-1946, 1965, 1974-1987 (Reel 47, Frame 197)
        - Teachers, 1975 (Reel 47, Frame 691)
        - Teamsters, 1940-1948 (Reel 47, Frame 712)
        - Truckers, Independent, 1974, 1983 (Reel 47, Frame 1083)
  - Historical Files
    - File 1: Chronological File
      - 1925?, Red International of Labor Unions (Reel 48, Frame 3)
      - 1928, Independent Communist League of Boston (Konikow Group), Bulletin (Reel 48, Frame 74)
      - 1929, CPUSA (Reel 48, Frame 87)
      - 1931, Communist League of America, Correspondence (Reel 48, Frame 110)
      - 1932
        - Communist League of America
          - Documents (Reel 48, Frame 130)
          - Unser Kampf (Reel 48, Frame 162)
          - Communistes, Greek section (Reel 48, Frame 182)
      - 1933
        - Shachtman essay Communism and the Negro (Reel 48, Frame 195)
        - Communist League of America, Documents (Reel 48, Frame 294)
        - Conference for Progressive Labor Action (1933-1934) (Reel 48, Frame 333)
      - 1934
        - American Workers Party (Reel 48, Frame 472)
        - Communist League of America (Reel 48, Frame 686)
        - Communist League of Struggle (Reel 48, Frame 805)
        - Non-partisan Labor Defense, 1934-1935 (Reel 48, Frame 814)
      - 1935
        - Revolutionary Workers League (includes International News, Volume 1, Numbers 6, 8-9) (Reel 49, Frame 3)
        - Workers Party documents (Reel 49, Frame 67)
        - Harlem branch minutes (Reel 49, Frame 366)
        - Young Peoples Socialist League vs. Clarity (Reel 49, Frame 383)
      - 1936
        - American Labor Party (Reel 49, Frame 442)
        - Communist League of America (Reel 49, Frame 451)
        - Revolutionary Workers League (Reel 49, Frame 454)
        - Socialist Party (Reel 49, Frame 470)
        - Workers Party, Documents (Reel 49, Frame 509)
      - 1937
        - Mooney defense (Reel 49, Frame 593)
        - Proletarian Party (Chicago) (Reel 49, Frame 597)
        - Revolutionary Workers League (Reel 49, Frame 608)
        - Socialist Party Documents (Reel 49, Frame 617)
        - Harry Milton letters from Spain (Reel 50, Frame 3)
      - 1938
        - 1938 Founding convention, Micro 596 (Reel 32, Othertype 18)
        - 1938-1939, Socialist Workers Party
          - Anti-fascist leaflets, Micro 2050 (Reel 50, Frame 38)
          - Correspondence (Reel 50, Frame 81)
          - Miscellaneous internal materials, Micro 596 (Reel 32, Othertype 22)
          - Miscellaneous international youth materials (1936-1940) (Reel 32, Othertype 23)
      - 1939-1940, Micro 2050 (Reel 50, Frame 93)
        - Russian discussion, Micro 596 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
        - Shachtman fight (Reel 32, Othertype 20)
      - 1940, Micro 2050
        - American Labor Party (Reel 50, Frame 215)
        - Committee for the 4th International (International Bulletin #1) (Reel 50, Frame 244)
        - Miscellaneous correspondence (Reel 50, Frame 261)
        - Emergency Conference, 4th Estate Clubs (Reel 50, Frame 283)
      - 1941
        - Grace Carlson tour (Reel 50, Frame 291)
        - Independent Labor League (Reel 50, Frame 367)
      - 1943, Phelan, Terence (Sherry Mangin) tour (Reel 50, Frame 376)
      - 1944
        - Revolutionary Workers League (Reel 50, Frame 382)
        - 1944-1947, Gerald L.K. Smith (Reel 50, Frame 409)
      - 1945
        - Miscellaneous correspondence (Reel 50, Frame 480)
        - Tours (Reel 50, Frame 519)
      - 1946
        - Carsten, Charles, Veterans Committee (Reel 50, Frame 603)
        - Goldman, Albert (Reel 50, Frame 653)
        - Konikow, Antoinette (Reel 50, Frame 665)
      - 1947, Fredericks (John) faction (Reel 50, Frame 678)
      - 1948-1952, Tours (Reel 50, Frame 685)
      - 1954, McCarthyism (Reel 50, Frame 890)
      - 1956, Muste correspondence (Reel 50, Frame 896)
      - 1956-1957, Stalinist regroupment (Reel 51, Frame 3)
      - 1957-1958
        - American Forum for Socialist Education (Reel 51, Frame 221)
        - Tours (Reel 51, Frame 691)
      - 1957-1959
        - United Independent-Socialist Campaign Committee
          - 1957 - 1958, September 9 (Reel 51, Frame 721)
          - 1958, September 12 - 1959 (Reel 52, Frame 3)
        - Wohlforth/Robertson and Youth (Reel 52, Frame 172)
      - 1959, Socialist literature barnstorming tour (Trailblazers) (Reel 52, Frame 219)
      - 1960, George Lincoln Rockwell (Reel 52, Frame 235)
      - 1961
        - 1961-1962, Committee on Party Fundraising (Reel 52, Frame 253)
        - Youth work (Wohlforth) (Reel 52, Frame 310)
      - 1962, Chicago Voters for Peace (Reel 52, Frame 343)
      - 1963, Labor Action for Peace minority reports (Reel 52, Frame 383)
      - 1963-1983, Kennedy assassination (Reel 52, Frame 437)
      - 1963-1965, Robertsonites expulsion (Spartacist League) (Reel 52, Frame 515)
      - 1963-1964, Student Committee for Travel to Cuba (Reel 52, Frame 552)
      - 1964, Youth (Reel 52, Frame 664)
      - 1964-1986, Lyndon LaRouche, Jr. (Reel 52, Frame 679)
      - 1966-1968, Peace and Freedom Party (Reel 53, Frame 3)
      - 1966-1970, Legion of Justice (Chicago) (Reel 53, Frame 125)
      - 1968, 1970-1973 Tours (Reel 53, Frame 286)
      - 1970, Sue's Story as Told by Five Women, film, CB 131
      - 1972-1973, Japan, Micro 2050 (Reel 53, Frame 594)
      - 1972-1973, Prisoners (Reel 53, Frame 609)
      - 1972-1973, David Weiss films (Reel 53, Frame 646)
      - 1973, Anti-inflation demonstration (Reel 53, Frame 672)
      - 1973-1974, CP electoral candidacies (Reel 53, Frame 726)
      - 1974, Anti-semitism (Reel 53, Frame 772)
      - 1974-1975, International correspondence (Reel 53, Frame 791)
      - 1974-1975, Miscellaneous correspondence (Reel 53, Frame 846)
      - 1974-1975, Soviet dissidents (Reel 54, Frame 3)
      - 1975, National Convention (Reel 54, Frame 77)
      - 1977-1978, Socialist and independent left electoral candidacies (Reel 54, Frame 108)
      - 1982
        - John Trinkl critique (Reel 54, Frame 177)
        - Plenum kit, 1985 (Reel 54, Frame 181)
        - Anti-apartheid/anti-war steering committee (Reel 54, Frame 448)
      - 1987
        - Active Workers conference committee (Reel 54, Frame 475)
        - Anti-Intervention demonstration committee (Reel 54, Frame 503)
        - SWP-GB discussions with Lutte Ouvriere (Reel 54, Frame 540)
      - 1989, Pathfinder Mural (Reel 54, Frame 558)
    - File 2: Organization File (Predecessors and older opposition groups)
      - American Workers Party, Miscellaneous materials, 1934, Micro 596 (Reel 32, Othertype 6)
      - Committee of an Appeal Left Wing (Most Group), Chicago Correspondence, 1937 (Reel 32, Othertype 16)
      - Communist League of America
        - Minutes, 1929, 1931-1934, Micro 2050 (Reel 55, Frame 4)
        - Youth Committee, Minutes, 1931-1933 (Reel 55, Frame 555)
        - Miscellaneous internal materials, 1932-1934, Micro 596 (Reel 32, Othertype 3-4)
        - Undated material, Micro 2050 (Reel 55, Frame 632)
      - Communist League of Struggle, Micro 596
        - The Struggle for Communism (Reel 33, Othertype 12)
        - The Struggle of the Unemployed, circa 1935 (Reel 33, Othertype 12)
      - Independent Socialist League
        - Forum, 1949-1957 (filmed without segments) (Reel 34)
        - Undated material, Micro 2050 (Reel 55, Frame 639)
      - Johnson-Forest Tendency (filmed without segment or frame numbers), 1947, Micro 596
        - Johnson-Forest Tendency Internal Bulletin, #1-12, 1947 (Reel 33)
        - Three Essays by Karl Marx (Reel 33)
        - The Invading Soviet Society (Reel 33)
        - World Revolutionary Perspectives and the Russian Question (Reel 33)
        - General documents, 1947-1951, undated, Micro 2050 (Reel 55, Frame 681)
      - League for a Revolutionary Workers Party (New International Bulletin, Volume 1, Numbers 1-3, 1935), Micro 596 (Reel 33, Othertype 5)
      - Revolutionary Workers League (Oehlerites) (International News, Volume 1, Numbers 1-5, 1935) (Reel 33, Othertype 13)
        - Undated material, Micro 2050 (Reel 55, Frame 854)
      - Socialist Appeal Institute minutes, 1937, February, Micro 596 (Reel 32, Othertype 15)
      - Socialist Party, Miscellaneous material
        - 1936-1937 (Includes some YPSL [Young Peoples Socialist League]) (Reel 32, Othertype 14)
        - 1940-1941, Micro 2050 (Reel 55, Frame 860)
        - Undated (Reel 55, Frame 882)
      - Spartacist Youth League
        - 1932-1934 (Reel 55, Frame 891)
        - 1935-1938 (Reel 56, Frame 3)
      - Workers Party
        - Plenums, Micro 596
          - 1935, June (Reel 32, Othertype 9)
          - 1935, October (Reel 32, Othertype 10)
        - Minutes, 1934-1936, Micro 2050 (Reel 56, Frame 233)
        - Miscellaneous materials
          - 1935-1936, Micro 596 (Reel 32, Othertype 11)
          - 1940-1948, Micro 2050 (Reel 56, Frame 383)
        - Publications (filmed without segment or frame numbers), Micro 596
          - Bulletin, 1943-1949 (Reel 34)
          - The Russian Question, 1941 (Reel 34)
          - Out of the Bureaucratic Jungle, circa 1944 (Reel 34)
          - Party Builder of the Workers Party, Volume II, Number 5, 1947 (Reel 34)
      - Young Peoples Socialist League, 1937-1945, Micro 2050 (Reel 56, Frame 478)
      - Youth Bureau for the Fourth International, International Bulletin, 1937 (Reel 56, Frame 695)
  - Opponents File (Recent Opposition Groups)
    - General reports on opponents, 1970-1977 (Reel 93, Frame 1)
    - American Labor Party, 1949 (Reel 93, Frame 216)
    - Communist Party USA
      - Anti-war leaflets, 1937-1940, undated (Reel 93, Frame 415)
      - Coney Island Club, 1973, undated (Reel 93, Frame 468)
      - Defense cases
        - General (Reel 93, Frame 493)
        - Angela Davis, 1971-1972 (Reel 93, Frame 537)
      - Notes, undated (Reel 93, Frame 591)
      - Relations with the SWP, 1956-1985 (Reel 93, Frame 618)
      - Study documents, circa 1940s (Reel 93, Frame 684)
      - Waterfront Section, 1946-1949 (Reel 94, Frame 1)
      - Chronological documents
        - 1930s-1973 (Reel 94, Frame 47)
        - 1974 - early 1980s, undated (Reel 95, Frame 1)
      - Communist Workers Party, 1981, 1985 (Reel 95, Frame 397)
      - Democrat Socialists, 1974-1976 (Reel 95, Frame 417)
      - DuBois Clubs of America
        - General, 1964-1972 (Reel 95, Frame 450)
        - Los Angeles, 1964 (Reel 95, Frame 782)
      - Guardian, 1974-1979 (Reel 95, Frame 809)
      - International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1940 (Reel 95, Frame 898)
      - Independent Progressive Party, 1948-1954 (Reel 95, Frame 855)
      - International Socialists, 1971, 1982 (Reel 95, Frame 901)
      - International Workers Party, 1980-1982 (Reel 96, Frame 1)
      - Libertarian Party, undated (Reel 96, Frame 83)
      - Line of March, 1983-1989 (Reel 96, Frame 95)
      - Maoists-General (Reel 96, Frame 152)
      - National Alliance Against Racism and Political Repression, 1972-1974 (Reel 96, Frame 158)
      - New American Movement, 1974-1979 (Reel 96, Frame 419)
      - New Left-General (Reel 96, Frame 435)
      - New Party of Florida, 1969 (Reel 96, Frame 441)
      - Pacifists, 1960-1967, undated (Reel 96, Frame 444)
      - Peace and Freedom Party, 1968-1971 (Reel 96, Frame 468)
      - People's Party, 1974 (Reel 96, Frame 534)
      - Progressive Labor Party, 1975 (Reel 96, Frame 538)
      - Progressive Youth Organizing Committee, 1961-1963 (Reel 96, Frame 543)
      - Rank and File Caucuses, Committee for, 1972 (Reel 96, Frame 597)
      - Revolutionary Communist Party, 1977-1980 (Reel 96, Frame 602)
      - Revolutionary Marxist Organizing Committee, 1976-1977 (Reel 96, Frame 735)
      - Revolutionary Socialist Party, 1977-1982 (Reel 97, Frame 1)
      - Revolutionary Student Brigade, 1975-1976 (Reel 97, Frame 117)
      - Revolutionary Workers League, undated (Reel 97, Frame 152)
      - Socialist Forum, 1974-1976 (Reel 97, Frame 156)
      - Socialist Labor Party, 1974-1988 (Reel 97, Frame 180)
      - Socialist Party, 1936-1940, undated (Reel 97, Frame 300)
      - Solidarity, 1987-1988 (Reel 97, Frame 309)
      - Spark, 1975-1976 (Reel 97, Frame 321)
      - Spartacist League, 1964-1988 (Reel 97, Frame 404)
      - Students for a Democratic Society, 1965-1969 (Reel 97, Frame 523)
      - Trotskyist Organization, 1976 (Reel 97, Frame 614)
      - War Resisters League, 1975-1976 (Reel 97, Frame 616)
      - Workers World Party, 1977-1980 (Reel 97, Frame 629)
      - Young Communist League, 1937-1990 (Reel 97, Frame 638)
      - Young Workers Liberation League, 1970-1976 (Reel 97, Frame 701)
  - Internal Discussions and Disputes
    - Appeals and resignations, 1983 (Reel 98, Frame 1)
    - Chinese Tendency, 1959-1965 (Reel 98, Frame 55)
    - Cochran Split, 1953 (Reel 98, Frame 216)
    - Communist Tendency (includes Vanguard), 1971 (Reel 98, Frame 285)
    - Ex-International Tendency, et cetera, 1979-1981 (Reel 98, Frame 357)
    - Fourth Internationalist Tendency, 1984-1991 (Reel 98, Frame 375)
    - Internationalist Tendency
      - 1972-1974 (Reel 98, Frame 445)
      - 1975-1977, undated (Reel 99, Frame 1)
    - Leninist Faction
      - Class Struggle League-Barbara Gregorich, 1971-1972 (Reel 99, Frame 384)
      - Communist Tendency, 1971-1973 (Reel 99, Frame 657)
    - Leavitt, Ralph, expulsion, 1971-1975 (Reel 99, Frame 800)
    - Merrill, Carol and Dick, expulsion, 1971 (Reel 99, Frame 886)
    - Proletarian Orientation, 1962-1966 (Reel 100, Frame 1)
    - Spartacist split, 1962-1964, undated (Reel 100, Frame 99)
    - Swabeck, Arne, 1964-1967 (Reel 100, Frame 194)
    - Socialist Action
      - Ban from SWP functions, 1984, 1990 (Reel 100, Frame 264)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1989 (Reel 100, Frame 282)
      - Information Bulletin, 1984, 1987-1988 (Reel 100, Frame 359)
      - Miah Fink book and related matters, 1990-1991 (Reel 100, Frame 464)
    - Tendency (1970-1972, undated) (Reel 100, Frame 533)
- Part 2 (Micro 2086): Additions, 1994-2000, Micro 2086; 24 reels of microfilm (35 mm)
  The additions of the New York Office of the Socialist Workers Party include minutes of the National Committee (NC) and the Political Committee (PC), bulletins, circulars, and correspondence distributed to the party leadership. There are gaps in the coverage. Minutes of the Political Bureau (PB) are included only for the year 2000. The correspondence, which consists of typed copies rather than original letters, was received only for the period 1994 to 1996. (January to March 1995 is also missing.) Branch Circulars are included for 1994 to 1996 only, and Information Bulletins are missing for 1995. Discussion Bulletins are missing for 1996 and for 1998 through 2000. The Young Socialist Discussion Bulletins are included for the years 1997 and 1998.
  - 1994
    - PC/NC Minutes
      - January-June (Reel 1, Frame 1)
      - July-December (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - Correspondence (Reel 2, Frame 1012)
    - Information Bulletins (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - Branch Circulars (Reel 3, Frame 55)
    - Discussion Bulletins (Reel 3, Frame 802)
  - 1995
    - PC/NC Minutes
      - January-June (Reel 4, Frame 1)
      - July-December (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - Correspondence, April-December, January-March not received. (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - Information Bulletins (Reel 6, Frame 192)
    - Branch Circulars (Reel 6, Frame 250)
    - Discussion Bulletins (Reel 6, Frame 976)
  - 1996, Discussion Bulletins not received.
    - PC/NC minutes
      - January-June (Reel 7, Frame 1)
      - July-December (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - Correspondence (Reel 8, Frame 1047)
    - Information Bulletins (Reel 8, Frame 1141)
    - Branch Circulars (Reel 9, Frame 1)
  - 1997, Correspondence and Branch Circulars not received.
    - PC/NC Minutes
      - January-June (Reel 10, Frame 1)
      - July-November (Reel 11, Frame 1)
      - December (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - Information Bulletins (Reel 12, Frame 1038)
    - Discussion Bulletins (Reel 12, Frame 1134)
    - YS Discussion Bulletins (Reel 12, Frame 1237)
  - 1998, Correspondence, Branch Circulars, and Discussion Bulletins not received.
    - PC/NC Minutes
      - January-April (Reel 13, Frame 1)
      - May-August (Reel 14, Frame 1)
      - September-December (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Information Bulletins (Reel 15, Frame 896)